riveroffers.com 2010-11-25

# RiverOffers.com Privacy Policy

RiverOffers.com is a web site that is owned and operated by Commission River, Inc. and owned subsidiary of Bayhill Capital OTC BB: BHYL

Our mailing address is:

12401 South 450 East, Suite D1  
Draper, UT 84020

## Privacy

Commission River, Inc. ("RiverOffers.com" or "we" or "us") uses this web site to run an affiliate marketing network over the World Wide Web (the "Web"). Even though Many portions of this web site are accessible and viewable by the general public, not all visitors may use our program. Each Commission River program is available for use only by persons or entities that join the network as either an "Affiliate" (Publisher), an "Advertiser" (Vendor), or "Strategic Partner" (Private Labeled Licensee).

## Information About Affiliates

When we receive a request to become a Commission River affiliate, that information is not shared with any third party for any reason. That information is used strictly for login security (when the affiliate accesses their password protected back office), tracking the sign up of new customers, and for payment of commissions. All affiliates have the ability to apply for all advertising programs offered without their individual information being shared in any way with our advertising partners.

## Information About Advertisers

Commission River advertisers are required to submit their contact and billing information to us when they apply to become listed in our program. Once approved, the Commission River team will build their products and/or services into our program and make them available to the community of affiliates. Commission River sends all new customer information (generated by affiliate traffic) directly to these advertisers for provisioning. Once the transaction in complete, the advertiser will pay Commission River for the sale. Commission River, in turn, pays the affiliate. The customer's private information never leaves this information loop.

## Information About Customers

After you order a product you will receive an automated confirmation email. You will never receive any general newsletter or other form of unsolicited mail that does not relate to your Telecom services purchase. Your information will not be shared, sold, rented, or traded with third parties for their promotional purposes.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file.

We set a persistent cookie to track the referring web site so that we may adequately track your quotes and compensate the appropriate affiliate partner who originally brought you to our site.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site without any change to your user experience.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) may use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by RiverOffers.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by using the "Contact Us" link, or contacting us at 12401 South 450 East, Suite D1, Draper, UT 84020 to opt-out.

## Additional Disclosures

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at poborn@telarus.com.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

If you have any question or comments that relate to our handling of your information may submit feedback using the "Contact Us" link.
